ugandaonline.net 2019-05-06

# Uganda Online - Uganda Online Website Directory Privacy Policy

April 05, 2009

**Privacy Policy for UgandOnline.net**

The privacy of our visitors to ugandaonline.net is important to us. 

At ugandaonline.net, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit ugandaonline.net, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your Internet Service Provider (ISP), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited and which pages you visited on Ugandaonline.net 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we use third party advertisements like (Google through the Adsense program) to serve ads on ugandaonline.net. Some of these advertisers use technologies such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which sends information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes like showing Uganda related ads to someone in Uganda, for example.

**DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).  This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). 

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Kampala, you may see Kampala hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about football).  DART uses “non personally identifiable information”.  It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.  You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting this [link](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)   

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. 

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.  Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**Your Consent**  
By Using our site, You consent to Ugandaonline.net privacy policy.

**Contact Us**  
In case you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, you can contact us on info@ugandaonline.net

**Updates**

Our Privacy policy will be updated as and when and all the updates will be shown here..
